// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
//HARD JS 
let questions = [
   

{
  numb:1,
  question:"Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using javascript?",
  answer:"C. Both A and B",
  options:[
  "A. getElementbyid()",
  "B. getElementsByClassName()",
  "C. Both A and B",
  "D. None of the above",
  ]
},

{
  numb:2,
  question:"Upon encountering empty statements,what does the javascript interpreter do?",
  answer:"B. Ignores a warning",
  options:[
  "A. Throws an error",
  "B. Ignores the statements",
  "C. Gives a warning",
  "D. None of the above",
  ]
},

{
  numb:3,
  question:"Which of the following methods can be used to display date in some form using javascript?",
  answer:"D. All the above",
  options:[
  "A. document write()",
  "B. console.lod()",
  "c. window alert()",
  "D. All the above",
  ]
},

{
  numb:4,
  question:"When interpretes encounters an empty statement, what it will do ?",
  answer:"D. Ignores the statement ",
  options:[
  "A. Shows a warning",
  "B. Promotes to complete the statement",
  "C. Throws an error",
  "D. Ignores the statement",
  ]
},

{
  numb:5,
  question:"Which one of the following also known as conditional expressions ?",
  answer:"A. Immediate if",
  options:[
  "A. Immediate if",
  "B. Alternative to if-else",
  "C. Switch statement",
  "D. If-then-else statement",
  ]
},

{
  numb:6,
  question:"Which of the following type of variable is volatile ?",
  answer:"A. Mutable variable",
  options:[
  "A. Mutable variable",
  "B. Dynamic variable",
  "C. Volatile variable",
  "D. None if the above",
  ]
},


{
  numb:7,
  question:"In the javascript, which one of the following is not considered as an error?",
  answer: "C. Division by zero",
  options:[
  "A. Syntax Error",
  "B. missing of semicolons",
  "C. Division by zero",
  "D. Missing of Bracket",
  ]
},

{
  numb:8,
  question:"Which one of the following is used for the calling a function or a method in the javascript?",
  answer:"B. Invocation Expression",
  options:[
  "A. Property Access Expression",
  "B. Invocation Expression",
  "C. Functional Expression",
  "D. Primary Expression",    
  ]
},

{
  numb:9,
  question:"Which one of the following is an ternary operator?",
  answer:"A. ?",
  options:[
  "A. ?",
  "B. :",
  "C. -",
  "D. +",    
  ]
},

{
  numb:10,
  question:"Which one of the following operator returns false if both values are equal?",
  answer:"A. !=",
  options:[
  "A. !+",
  "B. !==",
  "C. !",
  "D. All of the above",    
  ]
}


];